Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
- Series I. Assignments
  - June 1981
    - Million Dollar Class Ceremony, A10608 (Box 17)
    - Class of 1956, A10609 (Box 17)
    - Floyd Newman Arboretum Dedication, A10610 (Box 17)
    - Michael Slive, New Director of Athletics, A10611 (Box 17)
    - Floyd Newman Arboretum Dedication in Color, A10612 (Box 17)
  - July 1981
    - Hydroplant- Equipment Lift, A10702 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes- Ins and Outs, A10703 (Box 17)
    - Alan Savitzky with snake, A10706 (Box 17)
    - Alain Seznec and Alfred Kahn, A10708 (Box 17)
    - Cornell Adult University, A10710 (Box 17)
    - Uris Extension Construction, A10711 (Box 17)
  - August 1981
    - Back to School:, A10801 (Box 17)
    - Arrival, " (Box 17)
    - President's Convocation, Barton Hall, " (Box 17)
    - President with parents/Sheldon court/Campus scenes, " (Box 17)
    - Outdoor scenes/Barton Hall, " (Box 17)
    - Registration, " (Box 17)
    - Floyd Newman copy negative (writer age 3), A10802 (Box 17)
  - September 1981
    - Fun in the Sun '81, A10901 (Box 17)
    - Presidential Councillors visit Submicron, A10902 (Box 17)
    - Schuyler House dedication/dorm rooms (Chron.), A10903 (Box 17)
    - Campus bookstore/Career Fair, A10904 (Box 17)
    - Ag and Arts Quad Festival, A10905 (Box 17)
    - Hall of Fame/Football-Cornell vs Colgate, A10906 (Box 17)
    - Freshman Follies/Parents Weekend, A10907 (Box 17)
  - October 1981
    - Professor Norm Daly and Llhuros crates, A11001 (Box 17)
    - President Rhodes and United Fund/Commons in Anabel Taylor (Chron.), A11002 (Box 17)
    - Blood Drive/Sir Eric Ashby lecture at B & P A/B & P A candids/UAW Strike, A11003 (Box 17)
    - Indian Solidarity Day/Willard Straight activities, A11004 (Box 17)
    - James A. Baker Institute Dedication, A11005 (Box 17)
    - [Jim Maas Spouse], A11006 (Box 17)
    - Arts Quad Rally - World Com., A11007 (Box 17)
    - Ag Quad scenics/Human Ecology Computer opening (Chron.), A11008 (Box 17)
    - Stone Bridge Dedication, A11009 (Box 17)
    - Arts Quad Scenes, A11010 (Box 17)
    - Dedication, Knight Submicron Facility, A11011 (Box 17)
    - Clark Hall Machine Shop, A11012 (Box 17)
    - Roald Hoffmann, Nobel Prize, Chemistry, 1981, A11013 (Box 17)
    - Flood Waters, after the Rain, A11014 (Box 17)
  - November 1981
    - Gammelan in Lincoln Hall w/Guest Artist (Marty), A11101 (Box 17)
    - Fall Scenes, A11102 (Box 17)
    - Enzo Montemurro Memorial Service in Sage Chapel, A11103 (Box 17)
    - Eleanor Jordan; 'Sushi' Salesman; Language Classes in Morrill Hall (Chron.), A11104 (Box 17)
    - Nuclear Convocation in Bailey Hall, A11105 (Box 17)
    - Music VIP's and President Rhodes; Geological Sciences Building drawing (Chron.), A11106 (Box 17)
    - Engineering School; Concrete Lab, Classes, A11107 (Box 17)
    - Football: Cornell vs Columbia; Tailgating, Crowds, A11108 (Box 17)
    - Latin American Students on Campus, A11109 (Box 17)
    - School of Veterinary Medicine; Professors, classes, Multi-Cat., A11110 (Box 17)
    - Copy Negative: Latin American Students, from 35 mm color slide, A11111 (Box 17)
    - Hockey: Cornell vs Concordia (Randy), A11112 (Box 17)
    - Vance Christian, Endowed Chair, Hotel School, in Wine tasting Demonstration (Chron.), A11113 (Box 17)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Signature Book; Law School Rare Books Librarian (Marty), A11114 (Box 17)
  - December 1981
    - CU/Syracuse Basketball, A11201 (Box 17)
    - CU/Colgate Hockey, A11202 (Box 17)
    - Hangover/Group/Closeups, A11203 (Box 17)
    - Blood Pressure Testing Day, A11204 (Box 17)
    - Lewis Martin/Library Head, A11205 (Box 17)
    - Robert Barker/Bio. Sciences, A11206 (Box 17)
    - Binenkorb Center/GS, A11207 (Box 17)
    - Rockefeller Renovations/Bio. Sci. Exterior, A11208 (Box 17)
  - January 1982
    - News Bureau File / January --, A20101 (Box 17)
    - Uris Extension / Construction, A20102 (Box 17)
  - February 1982
    - News Bureau File / February-, A20201 (Box 17)
    - Engineering Week / Car & Tree / Quad, A20202 (Box 17)
    - Women Gymnastics / CU vs University of Mass, A20203 (Box 17)
    - Miss Piggy / Valentine / Campus Store, A20204 (Box 17)
    - Sports Weekends - Basketball/Wrestling/Hockey, A20205 (Box 17)
    - Snow scenes, A20206 (Box 17)
    - Rally / VIP's / Volunteers / Bus / Flags/ Space Science Building / Uris / A.D. White House, A20207 (Box 17)
    - Heptagonals, 1982, A20208 (Box 17)
  - March 1982
    - News Bureau, A20301 (Box 17)
    - Hydro Plant -, A20302 (Box 17)
    - Ice Sculpture/Brett Kahr, A20303 (Box 17)
    - 1000 Pt. Lucas/Basketball, A20304 (Box 17)
    - Snow scenes, A20305 (Box 17)
    - Green Dragon - St. Patrick's Day, A20306 (Box 17)
    - Vet School/Fregin/Nathanielsz, A20307 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes & Molisani - Johnson Art Gift, A20308 (Box 17)
    - Trustees/H & S/Development Breakfast, A20309 (Box 17)
    - Snow scenes, A20310 (Box 17)
  - April 1982
    - News Bureau, A20401 (Box 17)
    - Herbster & Energy Awards, A20402 (Box 17)
    - Spring/Outdoors/ Library Interiors, A20403 (Box 17)
    - Arts Quad / Sibley Dedication, A20404 (Box 17)
    - Engineering Exteriors / Computer Graphics, A20405 (Box 17)
    - Arts Quad / Morrill Language Class, A20406 (Box 17)
    - Curtis Sliwa-Guardian Angel Guest Speaker, A20407 (Box 17)
    - CU/Hobart Lacrosse & Earthball, A20408 (Box 17)
    - ROTC Awards, A20409 (Box 17)
    - Engineering Egg Drop, A20410 (Box 17)
    - Indonesian Microfilm Feature, A20411 (Box 17)
  - May 1982
    - News Bureau, A20501 (Box 17)
    - Phi Psi 500, A20502 (Box 17)
    - Vet School Students (four), A20503 (Box 17)
    - Springfest, A20504 (Box 17)
    - Campus scenes, A20505 (Box 17)
    - Knight Lab / Exteriors, A20506 (Box 17)
    - Lacrosse Crowd / Wee Stinky Glen Construction, A20507 (Box 17)
    - Science High School Students / Boyce Thompson, A20508 (Box 17)
    - Professor Isaacson/Submicron Facility, A20509 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes & Performing Arts Center Architect / Kiplinger, A20510 (Box 17)
    - Wee Stinky Glen '82 - '32 Reception/ Purcell, A20511 (Box 17)
    - Commencement, A20512 (Box 17)
  - June 1982
    - News Bureau, A20601 (Box 17)
    - Quad Scenes / Clouds, A20602 (Box 17)
    - Arboretum Dedication / Newman, A20603 (Box 17)
    - Reunion / Million Dollar Class, A20604 (Box 17)
    - Purcell Union Dedication, A20605 (Box 17)
    - 32 Wee Stinky Glen / Reunion, A20606 (Box 17)
    - 57 Crew Reunion, A20607 (Box 17)
    - Barton Booths / '57 at Balch, A20608 (Box 17)
    - Floyd Newman Copy Negative, A20609 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A20610 (Box 17)
  - July 1982
    - News Bureau, A20701 (Box 17)
    - Vet School, A20702 (Box 17)
    - Sailing, A20703 (Box 17)
  - August 1982
    - News Bureau, A20801 (Box 17)
    - Biological Sciences interiors, A20802 (Box 17)
    - Hydro-electric plant, " (Box 17)
    - Orientation, A20803 (Box 17)
  - September 1982
    - News Bureau, A20901 (Box 17)
    - Registration, A20902 (Box 17)
    - Fun in the Sun, A20903 (Box 17)
    - Jack Stilwell--Cook--30 year CU Employee / Balch Dining Scenes, A20904 (Box 17)
    - Travel Office, A20905 (Box 17)
    - University Press / Books / Exteriors / Howley, A20906 (Box 17)
    - Bio Sci Bldg. Dedication, A20907 (Box 17)
    - Copy Neg of John M. Olin made from B & W Portrait, A20908 (Box 17)
    - The Wall at Uris Library Extension, A20909 (Box 17)
    - Uris Library Extension--Interiors & Exteriors, A20910 (Box 17)
    - Presentation--Rhodes Office, A20911 (Box 17)
    - Uris Library Extension/ Dedication, A20912 (Box 17)
    - Bio Science/ Morrison Room, A20913 (Box 17)
    - Football/ Employee/ Rhodes/ Hall of Fame, A20914 (Box 17)
    - Gorge Closing Sign/ Esther Spielman--United Way/ Employee Kim Goodwin/ Tropical Greenhouse, A20915 (Box 17)
  - October 1982
    - News Bureau, A21001 (Box 17)
    - Library/ Straight/ Students, A21002 (Box 17)
    - Baker Institute, A21003 (Box 17)
    - Exxon Head - Garvin, A21004 (Box 17)
    - Open Neg File #, A21005 (Box 17)
    - Cheerleading/ Football, A21006 (Box 17)
    - Nobel Laureate Ken Wilson with Roald Hoffman and Hans Bethe, A21007 (Box 17)
    - Major Donor Presentations:, A21008 (Box 17)
    - Mr. Hatfield, " (Box 17)
    - Mrs. Uris, " (Box 17)
    - Helen & F.R. Newman, " (Box 17)
    - Mr. Kroch, " (Box 17)
    - Homecoming/ Barton, A21009 (Box 17)
    - Photo Record on Newman Arboretum Dedication Album, A21010 (Box 17)
    - Geology Groundbreaking (On site groundbreaking, donor presentation to Mrs. Snee, reception following groundbreaking), A21011
      - Contact sheet (Box 17)
    - Dress rehersal of Cornell Play, A21012 (Box 17)
    - Reception following opening performance of play, " (Box 17)
    - Copy Negative (4" x 5") of Class '57 Crew Team Group Photo, A21013 (Box 17)
    - Football, A21014 (Box 17)
    - Foorball, A21015 (Box 17)
    - Presentation of Women's Crew Shell, A21016 (Box 17)
    - Class of '48 meeting, A21017 (Box 17)
    - Phonathon, A21018 (Box 17)
    - New Athletic Pads, A21019 (Box 17)
    - Halloween Contest, A21020 (Box 17)
    - Fundraising Kickoff, A21021 (Box 17)
  - November 1982
    - News Bureau:, A21101 (Box 17)
    - 50th Anniversary Celebration of Myron Taylor Hall / work on Tower, " (Box 17)
    - MootCourt Room Trials, " (Box 17)
    - Donor Presentations (Kettering, Miller) / Cornell Theatre, A21102 (Box 17)
    - TIAA-CREF Retirement Lecture, A21103 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A21104 (Box 17)
    - E. Richard Hoebeke (Entomology) / Cornell Insect Collection, A21105 (Box 17)
    - C.U.-Penn Game / Blackman, A21106 (Box 17)
  - December 1982
    - News Bureau, A21201 (Box 17)
    - Development:, A21202 (Box 17)
    - Phonathon Kickoff, " (Box 17)
    - Corporate Gift / NL Industry presentations, " (Box 17)
    - Berens/Rhodes donor presentations, " (Box 17)
    - Roberts Hall exteriors, Biological Sciences interiors, A21203 (Box 17)
    - Biological Sciences interiors, construction, Malott Hall, " (Box 17)
    - Mudd building (Bio. Sci.), Infant Vision Experiment (Prof. Howland), " (Box 17)
    - Derrick Harmon/ Rhodes/ General Motors presentation for CU Scholarships, A21204 (Box 17)
  - January 1983
    - Subject(s), Negative Number (Box 17)
    - News Bureau (CACO Conference), A30101 (Box 17)
    - Development [None], A30102 (Box 17)
    - Vet College Administration, A30103 (Box 17)
    - Cornell Electron Storage Ring (CESR) researchers, B-meson, at Synchrotron, A30104 (Box 17)
    - Maxie Baughan press conference, A30105 (Box 17)
    - CU/Columbia basketball game (1/29/83), A30106 (Box 17)
  - February 1983
    - News Bureau:, A30201 (Box 17)
    - CU/RPI Hockey Game, " (Box 17)
    - CU/Yale Hockey Game, " (Box 17)
    - Development Office:, A30202 (Box 17)
    - Arts College Reception, " (Box 17)
    - Phonathon, Referral Center, " (Box 17)
    - Phonathon, " (Box 17)
    - CACO Conference; Phonathon, " (Box 17)
    - Phonathon, " (Box 17)
    - Phonathon, " (Box 17)
    - Peter Nathaniel/Vet College, " (Box 17)
    - Sigma Chi winning Phonathon team, " (Box 17)
    - Sri Lanka Table; CU/Penn Basketball Game, A30203 (Box 17)
    - Veterinary College (Ann Marcham), A30204 (Box 17)
    - Nabokov Exhibit (Olin Library); Bloodmobile at Willard Straight Hall; Black Gospel, A30205 (Box 17)
    - 7th Annual Black Gospel Weekend, A30206 (Box 17)
    - CU/Penn Game; student with model airplanes on Arts quad; Herakles statue (by Jason Seeley) at Johnson Art Museum, A30207 (Box 17)
    - Test roll for Kodak b/w services (Campus Store and Willard Straight Hall, students), A30208 (Box 17)
  - March 1983
    Negatives for photographs later than A30309 are held in the Visual Services Department in Comstock Hall, as of February 1994.
    - News Bureau, A30301 (Box 17)
    - Development Office:, A30302 (Box 17)
    - I & LR, Nick Salvatore, A30302 (Box 17)
    - Vet College, Dr. Nathanielsz, A30302 (Box 17)
    - Chimes and crane / Ag Day / Student with papers flying, A30303 (Box 17)
    - Sailplane ("Tuck" Staggs, '86) / Dorm Rooms, A30304 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes and Arts School Seniors Luncheon, A30305 (Box 17)
    - Chemistry Labs / John M. Thomas, lecturer, A30306 (Box 17)
    - Green Dragon parade, A30307 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes and band album presentation / Willard Straight interiors (dining), A30308 (Box 17)
    - Copy negatives: Performing Arts Center (drawing, model); Gil Goetz talk boards; Arecibo gas cloud pattern, A30309 (Box 17)
  - April 1983
    - News Bureau, A30401 (Box 17)
    - Development Office, A30402 (Box 17)
    - Olin Library, A30403 (Box 17)
    - Campus Store / Books, A30404 (Box 17)
    - Lacrosse (CU/Penn), A30405 (Box 17)
    - NBC-TV Coverage, Hollis Cornell Auditorium, A30406 (Box 17)
    - Ed Marinaro visit, A30407 (Box 17)
    - Vet College Open House, A30408 (Box 17)
    - Herbster and Employee Awards, A30409 (Box 17)
    - Jorge Luis Borges and Dmitri Nabokov visit, A30410 (Box 17)
    - Japanese Museum visitors / Arthur Dean Book Award winner, A30411 (Box 17)
    - Livestock Show at Pavilion, A30412 (Box 17)
    - Dale Corson and new computer / snow scenes, A30413 (Box 17)
    - Fontanas Contest: "Raunchiest Sneakers", A30414 (Box 17)
    - Loan collectors (Bursar's Office) / campus scenes, A30415 (Box 17)
    - A.S.C.E. Bridge Contest at Hollister, A30416 (Box 17)
    - *New file started "Livestock Pavillion". (Also started a new file, "Computers" G 26 (Box 17)
  - May 1983
    - News Bureau:, A30501 (Box 17)
    - Maxie Baughan, " (Box 17)
    - Paul Pritchard, " (Box 17)
    - Shoals Marine Lab, " (Box 17)
    - Development Office:, A30502 (Box 17)
    - 1983 Senior Class Reception, Cornell Fund, " (Box 17)
    - Engineering School Bridge Project, " (Box 17)
    - Class of 1959 Reunion Planning Meeting, " (Box 17)
    - Bridge; Geological Sciences, " (Box 17)
    - Lacrosse (CU/Princeton game), A30503 (Box 17)
    - Anything-That-Floats-But-Not-A-Boat, A30504 (Box 17)
    - Willard Straight exteriors and facetime, A30505 (Box 17)
    - Phi Psi 500, A30506 (Box 17)
    - Health Awareness Day (Willard Straight Hall), A30507 (Box 17)
    - Engineering Quad bash, A30508 (Box 17)
    - Brown Bag lunch (Frank Rhodes and employees), A30509 (Box 17)
    - Springfest '83, A30510 (Box 17)
    - Engineering Bridge Construction (before), A30511 (Box 17)
    - Dr. Szalay/ Boyce Thompson Institute, A30512 (Box 17)
    - Kevin Lee/ Clark Hall experiment, A30513 (Box 17)
    - Engineering Bridge Construction (after), A30514 (Box 17)
    - 1983 Commencement, A30515 (Box 17)
  - June 1983
    - News Bureau:, A30601 (Box 17)
    - Development:, A30602 (Box 17)
    - 1983 Reunion, " (Box 17)
    - Library Associates, " (Box 17)
    - Bob Storant, " (Box 17)
    - 1983 Reunion, A30603 (Box 17)
    - Robert Wilson and sculpture, A30604 (Box 17)
  - July 1983
    - News Bureau:, A30701 (Box 17)
    - Development (10 frames), A30702 (Box 17)
    - Crop Loss Assessment Prog. With Roger Kohut (For Roger), A30703 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A30704 (Box 17)
    - Clothes for Handicapped (Gret Atkin) Knight Lab/ A.D. White House, A30705 (Box 17)
    - Gannett Clinic, A30706 (Box 17)
  - August 1983
    - News Bureau:, A30801 (Box 17)
    - Development, A30802 (Box 17)
    - Info Center Computer Terminal, A30803 (Box 17)
    - Orientation, A30804 (Box 17)
    - Football/ Alumni/ Baughn/ Luncheon, A30805 (Box 17)
    - Offbet Olympics, A30806 (Box 17)
  - September 1983
    - News Bureau, A30901 (Box 17)
    - Development, A30902 (Box 17)
    - Fun In The Sun, A30903 (Box 17)
    - Roald Hoffman/ IHS Group/ Campus Scenes, A30904 (Box 17)
    - CU - Colgate Stuff, A30905 (Box 17)
    - Employee Day, A30906 (Box 17)
  - October 1983
    - News Bureau, A31001 (Box 17)
    - Development, A31002 (Box 17)
    - Plantations Fall-In, A31003 (Box 17)
    - Tom Allen/ Football, A31004 (Box 17)
    - Dave Burn[l?], A31005 (Box 17)
    - Trustee Weekend '83, A31006 (Box 17)
    - Richard Farr & Humphrey Bldg., A31007 (Box 17)
    - Arboretum (Color), A31008 (Box 17)
    - United Way & Campus Scenes, A31009 (Box 17)
    - Ben Mintz, Floyd Schwartz Walder & Arnie Burdick with Cornell Book, A31010 (Box 17)
    - Halloween Competition at Campus Store, A31011 (Box 17)
  - November 1983
    - News Bureau, A31101 (Box 17)
    - Development, A31102 (Box 17)
    - Prof. Scheraga, A31103 (Box 17)
    - Turkeys, A31104 (Box 17)
    - Fall Scenes, Rhodes, A31105 (Box 17)
    - Personnel Dept., A31106 (Box 17)
    - Harriet Ink United Way, A31107 (Box 17)
    - Alice Cook Birthday, A31108 (Box 17)
  - December 1983
    - News Bureau - Anna Moratz 1, A31201 (Box 17)
    - Development, A31202 (Box 17)
    - Personnel - On going, A31203 (Box 17)
    - Ted Arps / Jamie Beatty - cornell dining Internships, A31204 (Box 17)
    - Modern Indonesia Project, A31205 (Box 17)
    - Prof. Kennedy - Stmson, A31206 (Box 17)
  - January 1984
    - News Bureau, A40101 (Box 17)
    - Development, A40102 (Box 17)
    - Murray Death Roast, A40103 (Box 17)
    - Computers, A40104 (Box 17)
    - Winter Scenes, A40105 (Box 17)
    - Reg, Snow, Const, A40106 (Box 17)
    - Vet School, A40107 (Box 17)
    - Baker Institute, A40108 (Box 17)
    - Campus Store & Outdoors Scenes, A40109 (Box 17)
  - February 1984
    - News Bureau, A40201 (Box 17)
    - Development, A40202 (Box 17)
    - Personnel (on going), A40203 (Box 17)
    - Basketball (Harvard), A40204 (Box 17)
    - Tim Teitelbaum (Computer), A40205 (Box 17)
    - Personnel (Alicia Plotkin, Cecil Murphy), A40206 (Box 17)
    - Chemistry (David Usher), A40207 (Box 17)
    - Law School (Libe/ Interiors), A40208 (Box 17)
    - Structures (clark Hall), A40209 (Box 17)
    - Maydew-Controllers Office, A40210 (Box 17)
    - Quad/Scenes/Misc., A40211 (Box 17)
    - CU/ Princeton Basketball, A40212 (Box 17)
    - Personnel, Phonathon, Rats in Space, A40213 (Box 17)
    - Jean Novacco, Kim Smith, A40214 (Box 17)
  - March 1984
    - News Bureau, A40301 (Box 17)
    - Development, A40302 (Box 17)
    - Irish/Cajun music/ Statler, A40303 (Box 17)
    - Ted Lowi, A40304 (Box 17)
    - Academic II, Campus Scenes, A40305 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, Ag Day, Demonstration, A40306 (Box 17)
    - Green Dragon, A40307 (Box 17)
    - Ag Day, A40308 (Box 17)
    - Kiplinger (Copy Negative), A40309 (Box 17)
    - Cornell Trad/ Brochure, A40310 (Box 17)
    - Sam McNeal/ Rhodes/ Trustees, A40311 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A40312 (Box 17)
    - Sue Murphy/ May Hines, A40313 (Box 17)
  - April 1984
    - News Bureau, A40401 (Box 17)
    - Development, A40402 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes - check passing, A40403 (Box 17)
    - Snow Scenes, A40404 (Box 17)
    - Copy Negs. Sanford Weill/Kenneth Blanchard, A40405 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes/ Joan Burgett, A40406 (Box 17)
    - CU/Yale Lacrosse, A40407 (Box 17)
    - Moran/ Hall of Fame, A40408 (Box 17)
    - Livestock/ Milkshake/ Vet Open House, A40409 (Box 17)
    - Kazmerski/ Frankovic Campus Scenes, A40410 (Box 17)
    - Herbster Awards, A40411 (Box 17)
    - Syracuse/CU Lacrosse, A40412 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes/ Gannet, A40413 (Box 17)
    - David Ruether/ CS, A40414 (Box 17)
    - N. Kazmerski/ Student Awards, A40415 (Box 17)
    - Phi Psi 500, A40416 (Box 17)
    - Arbor Day/ CS, A40417 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A40418 (Box 17)
  - May 1984
    - News Bureau, A40501 (Box 17)
    - Development, A40502 (Box 17)
    - Netter/Ramus -- ILR School, A40503 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes/ Peter & Wolf/ Risley Fair, A40504 (Box 17)
    - David Reuther, A40505 (Box 17)
    - Peter Kahn, A40506 (Box 17)
    - Ornithology/ Falcons, A40507 (Box 17)
    - Spring Fest/ Pine tree Guy, A40508 (Box 17)
    - Lacrosse, A40509 (Box 17)
    - CRC Meat Cutting/ Clark Awards/ Campus scenes, A40510 (Box 17)
    - Al Armstrong, A40511 (Box 17)
    - 18th Hole/ Mrs. J. Noyes, A40512 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes & New Employees, A40513 (Box 17)
    - Commencement, A40514 (Box 17)
    - WHCU Group, A40515 (Box 17)
    - Myron and Anabel Taylor: Copy Negative, A40516 (Box 17)
    - Executive Staff/ Rhodes/ Groups, A40517 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes & Honor Students, A40518 (Box 17)
  - June 1984
    - News Bureau, A40601 (Box 17)
    - Development, A40602 (Box 17)
    - Birth Mule/Equine, A40603 (Box 17)
    - Thomas/ Tarr, A40604 (Box 17)
    - EAP, A40605 (Box 17)
    - Alumni Reunion, A40606 (Box 17)
    - Clark CAB, A40607 (Box 17)
    - Quad Scenes/ Zoom test, A40608 (Box 17)
  - July 1984
    - News Bureau, A40701 (Box 17)
    - Development, A40702 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes/ IBM Check, A40703 (Box 17)
    - Fierworks, A40704 (Box 17)
    - Class of 34/ flag, A40705 (Box 17)
    - Jazz Bands/ Arts Quad, A40706 (Box 17)
    - Fruitstand/ Aerobics, A40707 (Box 17)
    - Horsie II, A40708 (Box 17)
  - august 1984
    - Infant Day Care (Anna Moratz), A40801 (Box 18)
    - Development, A40802 (Box 18)
    - Malott/ summer conference, A40803 (Box 18)
    - Dean McMinn, A40804 (Box 18)
    - IBM Computers Project EZRA, A40805 (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes, A40806 (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes, A40807 (Box 18)
    - Horsie III More Horsie II, A40808 (Box 18)
    - Professor Steve Emlen, A40809 (Box 18)
    - Marilyn Paluba/ Registrars Office/ Gloria Howell, A40810 (Box 18)
    - Student Family Fair, A40811 (Box 18)
    - Orientation/ Rhodes Convocation, A40812 (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes, A40813 (Box 18)
    - Offbeat Olympics, A40814 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Frolic, A40815 (Box 18)
    - B & W Presidential Councillors, A40816 (Box 18)
    - Color Negatives Presidential Coun., A40817 (Box 18)
    - Registration and IDs, A40818 (Box 18)
    - Mare and calf, A40819 (Box 18)
    - Barry Adams, New Vice Provost, A40820 (Box 18)
  - September 1984
    - News Bureau, A40901 (Box 18)
    - Development, A40902 (Box 18)
    - Gil Goetz Publicity pics, A40903 (Box 18)
    - Hockey Lines/ Campus Scenes, A40904 (Box 18)
    - Fun in the Sun, A40905 (Box 18)
    - Career Fair, A40906 (Box 18)
    - Arnot Forest Exposition, A40907 (Box 18)
    - CU/ Princeton Football, A40908 (Box 18)
    - Snee Building Interiors, A40909 (Box 18)
    - IBM Computers at ILR, A40910 (Box 18)
    - CU/Colgate--Employee Day, A40911 (Box 18)
    - Uris Aud., A40912 (Box 18)
    - Salpeter open house, A40913 (Box 18)
  - October 1984
    - News Bureau, A41001 (Box 18)
    - Development, A41002 (Box 18)
    - New Computer Facility @ Uris/ William Bassett, A41003 (Box 18)
    - Wm. Bassett head shots/ A & T and Matyas Phone signing, A41004 (Box 18)
    - Africana Center Conference/ Snee building Ext., A41005 (Box 18)
    - Indian exhibition/ edwin Salpeter, A41006 (Box 18)
    - Rhodes/ Lundine/ Fuqus, A41007 (Box 18)
    - Snee Dedication/ Ghost of (Double exposed), A41008 (Box 18)
    - McTague Speaker, A41009 (Box 18)
    - Performing Arts/ Ground Breaking, A41010 (Box 18)
    - Johnson Endowment to Business School*, A41011 (Box 18)
    - Mario Cuomo, A41012 (Box 18)
    - NLRB Conference, A41013 (Box 18)
    - Steve Kaplan, A41013A (Box 18)
    - Football, A41014 (Box 18)
    - Copesetics/ CU Brown Football, A41015 (Box 18)
    - Energy Award/ Doney, A41016 (Box 18)
    - Pumpkin Selling, A41017 (Box 18)
    - Apple Harvest, A41018 (Box 18)
    - Tot Parade Halloween at Hasbrouck Apts., A41019 (Box 18)
    - Toxicology Conference, A41020 (Box 18)
    - *Trustee Council weekend are interspersed throughout Johnson Endowments (Box 18)
  - November 1984
    - News Bureau, A41101 (Box 18)
    - Development, A41102 (Box 18)
    - Law Enforcement Award, A41103 (Box 18)
    - Dr. Robert Pohl, A41104 (Box 18)
    - Ground Smashing, Clark, A41105 (Box 18)
    - Karen Vogtmann, A41106 (Box 18)
    - Gymnastics, A41107 (Box 18)
  - December 1984
    - News Bureau, A41201 (Box 18)
    - Development, A41202 (Box 18)
    - Cornell Scientists Journal Sale, A41203 (Box 18)